<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle">
  <channel>
    <title>Eduverse Changelog</title>
    <description>Most recent updates to Eduverse</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Version 1.5.2</title>
      <sparkle:version>1.5.2+21</sparkle:version>
      <eduverse:force>false</eduverse:force>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <h2>🚀 What's New in 1.5.2</h2>
          
          <h3>📅 Academic Planning & Syllabus</h3>
          <ul>
            <li><strong>Syllabus Visual Guide:</strong> Added "Table of Contents" dotted leaders and interactive row-hover highlighting to make reading complex curriculum hierarchies effortless.</li>
            <li><strong>Intelligent Planning:</strong> Integrated real-time "Planning vs. Syllabus" coverage cards with exact "out of" counts for Topics and SLOs.</li>
            <li><strong>Global Logic:</strong> The system now enforces year-wide uniqueness, preventing the same topic from being planned twice across different weeks.</li>
            <li><strong>Total Pages:</strong> Automatic calculation and display of total subject pages based on chapter configurations.</li>
          </ul>

          <h3>👨‍🏫 Teacher & Workload Management</h3>
          <ul>
            <li><strong>Redesigned Workload UI:</strong> Teacher assignments are now elegantly grouped by Classroom using the new <code>TigleGroupedCard</code> molecule.</li>
            <li><strong>Analytics Refinement:</strong> Replaced "Strength" with "Workload" (cumulative student count) while maintaining "Unique Reach" visibility in stat summaries.</li>
            <li><strong>Smart Constraints:</strong> Added validation to prevent logically conflicting assignments (e.g., assigning "General/All" alongside specific subjects).</li>
          </ul>

          <h3>📊 Data Integrity & Reporting</h3>
          <ul>
            <li><strong>Clean Sweep Deletion:</strong> Deleting a Classroom now performs a full cascading purge of all associated Syllabus data, Weekly Plans, and History to prevent orphaned records.</li>
            <li><strong>Enhanced Audit Trails:</strong> Delivery review reports now explicitly list "Missed Topics" and their associated reasons in text exports.</li>
          </ul>

          <h3>✨ UI / UX & Design System</h3>
          <ul>
            <li><strong>High-Alert Redesign:</strong> Fully overhauled destructive dialogs with a modern "Alert Container" style, centered typography, and high-contrast block actions.</li>
            <li><strong>Desktop Optimization:</strong> Standardized dialog widths and fixed "stretched" layouts on large monitors.</li>
            <li><strong>TigleKit Expansion:</strong> Migrated multiple application patterns into standard UI Kit molecules: <code>TigleGroupedCard</code>, <code>TigleProgressCard</code>, and <code>TigleHierarchyPicker</code>.</li>
          </ul>

          <h3>🛠️ Bug Fixes</h3>
          <ul>
            <li>Fixed a layout crash in Stat Cards when used within scrollable horizontal rows.</li>
            <li>Fixed hover highlights missing on sub-topics due to hit-test transparency.</li>
            <li>Resolved an issue where Snackbars appeared behind modal editor sheets.</li>
            <li>Fixed "Null check operator" crashes when viewing empty history detail headers.</li>
          </ul>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 04:25:00 +0500</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/AssabTigleG/ota_updates/releases/download/Release/eduverse_setup.exe"
                 sparkle:version="1.5.2+21"
                 sparkle:os="windows"
                 length="0" 
                 type="application/octet-stream" />
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
